Guide to the William David Allred Papers 1969-002
University of Houston Libraries Special Collections
William David Allred Papers
1966-1985
Special Collections, University of Houston Libraries
Allred, William David, 1933-1996
1969-002
105 Linear Feet
Democratic representative of District 13 in the Texas State House of Representatives, 1966-1980. Collection includes correspondence, publications, notes, and other materials pertaining to a variety of individuals and subjects from across Allred's political career.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for Research.
Acquisition Information
Information of acquisition method not available.
Biographical / Historical
William David Allred was born in Austin, Texas on November 27, 1933 to Governor James V. Allred and Joe Betsy Miller. After receiving a Bachelor of Arts in Journalism and English from Texas Christian University in 1955, Allred enlisted in the United States Army. During his two year stint, Allred served as a Public Relations Officer at Forts Eustis and Story. He was discharged from active duty as a second lieutenant in 1957, remaining active in the Army Reserves for more than twenty years.
Following his military service, Allred received his Master of Arts in Journalism from Columbia University in 1961. Allred immediately began work as a reporter, working as a Washington DC correspondent for media outlets such as the Wichita Falls Times and Record-News, the Houston Post, and the Associated Press. During this period, Allred also served in public relations for numerous Congressional offices.
After returning to Wichita Falls, Texas, Allred was elected to represent District 13 in the Texas State House of Representatives in 1966. In his 14 years of service, Allred championed causes related to ethics reform and served on the House Appropriations Committee, the Health and Welfare Commission, the Committee on Business and Industry, the Committee on Social Services, and more. Allred's commitment to public service over self is often noted; Allred was known to live in his congressional office in order to save on rent costs and make ends meet. Allred remained active in other pursuits during his terms in office, managing the press for Dolph Briscoe's 1968 run for governor, practicing as a licensed minister, and becoming a certified attorney in 1978.
Following the conclusion of his legislative career, Allred followed up on his other pursuits, serving as an Assistant Attorney General under Jim Mattox, continuing work as a minister, and eventually serving as a professor of journalism at the University of Texas at Austin, Hampton University, and Radford University. Allred died on September 8, 1996 at the age of 62.
67th Texas State Legislature. House. Resolutions – Congratulatory and Honorary. H.C.R. No. 48. 1991. https://lrl.texas.gov/scanned/members/honorary/67/Allred_Dave_HCR48.pdf 75th Texas State Legislature. House. Resolutions – Memorial. H.R. No. 25. March 20, 1997. https://lrl.texas.gov/scanned/members/memorial/75/75_Allred_hr25.pdf "William David Allred." Texas State Cemetery. https://cemetery.tspb.texas.gov/pub/user_form.asp?pers_id=3236
Related Materials
James V. Allred Papers, Special Collections, University of Houston Libraries.
Scope and Contents
The William David Allred Papers consist of 105 boxes of material dating from 1966 to 1985 that document Allred's service in the Texas State House of Representatives and as Assistant Attorney General. A Political Files series comprises the bulk of this collection, containing correspondence, publications, notes, and other materials pertaining to a variety of individuals and topics that Allred dealt with over the course of his 14-year political career. This series is arranged according to Allred's original alphabetical filing system and provides rich insight into Allred's role as an elected representative and myriad economic, social, and political aspects of the history of Texas. Reports and Publications and a Press Files series round out the collection, documenting Allred's work through official congressional reports and outside media coverage.
Houston (Tex.) -- Politics and government; Political Campaigns -- Texas; Texas. Legislature; Correspondence; Reports; Clippings (information artifacts); Allred, William David, 1933-1996
- Political File, 1966-1980
  - Abbott, Cathy (Box 1)
  - Abbott, Carroll (Box 1)
  - Abbott, M. L. (Box 1)
  - Abdnor, John (Box 1)
  - Abel, Bobby (Box 1)
  - Abertnathy, L.V. "Bud" (Box 1)
  - Abilene Christian College (Box 1)
  - Abington, William H. (Box 1)
  - Aboussie, Miss Josephine (Box 1)
  - Aboussie, Karen (Box 1)
  - Aboussie, Kenneth (Dr.) (Box 1)
  - Aboussie, Miss Marilyn (Box 1)
  - Aboussie, Philip Joe (Box 1)
  - Aboussie, Mr. T. A. (Box 1)
  - Abraham, Mr. & Mrs. Frank (Box 1)
  - Academic Freedom (Box 1)
  - Accountants (Box 1)
  - Accounting (Box 1)
  - Acker, Mr. & Mrs. Dewitt (Box 1)
  - Ackerman, Dick (Box 1)
  - Action Coalition of Texas (Box 1)
  - Acton, George B. (Box 1)
  - Adair, Joe N., Sr. (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box 1)
  - Adair, John W. (Mr.) (Box 1)
  - Adams, George G. (Box 1)
  - Adams, Herman (Rep.) (Box 1)
  - Adams, Hershel S. (Box 1)
  - Adams, Mrs. Lucille (Box 1)
  - Adams, O.T. (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box 1)
  - Adams, Mr. & Mrs. Raymond (Box 1)
  - Adams, Rex (Mrs.) (Box 1)
  - Adams, Richard (Box 1)
  - Adjutant General's Department (Box 1)
  - Adoption (Box 1)
  - Admire, Ms. Pearl (Box 1)
  - Advisory Council for Technical- Vocational Education in Texas (Box 1)
  - Aero Technical Institute (Box 1)
  - AFL - CIO File 1 (Box 1)
  - AFL - CIO File 2 (Box 1)
  - Agency Shop (Box 1)
  - Aging File 1 (Box 1)
  - Aging File 2 (Box 1)
  - Agnew, Bob (Box 1)
  - Agnew, Spiro (Box 1)
  - Agnich, Hon. Fred J. (Box 1)
  - Alikin, Senator A. M., Jr. (Box 1)
  - Air Conditioning (Box 1)
  - Air Control Board (Box 1)
  - Air Force (Box 1)
  - Air Force Association (Box 1)
  - Air Force Village Foundation, Inc. (Box 1)
  - Air Pollution (Box 1)
  - Alabama-Coushatta Indians (Box 1)
  - Albert, Bobby (Mr.) (Box 1)
  - Albert, E. O. (Mrs.) (Box 1)
  - Albritton, Ruth D. (Box 1)
  - Alcorn, Gwenlyn (Box 1)
  - Alcorn, Jimmy (Box 1)
  - Alexander, C.R. (Box 1)
  - Alexander, D.L. (Box 1)
  - Alexander, Don (Box 1)
  - Alexander, J.C. (Box 1)
  - Alexander, Jim R. (Box 1)
  - Alexander, Joe (Box 1)
  - Alexander, Mr. Pericles (Box 1)
  - Alexander, Sheryl (Box 1)
  - Alexander, Ted C., Jr. (Dr.) (Box 1)
  - Alford, David G. (Box 1)
  - Alford, Fred (Box 1)
  - Alford, John (Box 1)
  - Alladin Beauty Colleges, Inc. (Box 1)
  - Allbritton, Joe L. (Box 1)
  - Allen, Beth (Box 1)
  - Allen, Dr. David H. (Box 1)
  - Allen, Kenneth R. (Box 1)
  - Allen, Henry (Box 1)
  - Allen, James Leroy (Box 1)
  - Allen, Jerry W. (Box 1)
  - Allen, Joe (Box 1)
  - Allen, John (Rep. & Mrs.) (Box 1)
  - Allen, Joyce (Box 1)
  - Allen, Mrs. Marie (Box 1)
  - Allen, Musette (Box 1)
  - Allen, Robert Wayne (Box 1)
  - Allen, Woody (Box 1)
  - Allis-Chalmer (Box 1)
  - Allison, A. T., Jr. Allison Pharmacy (Box 1)
  - Allison, Howard (Box 1)
  - Allison, Laura (Miss) (Box 1)
  - Allison, Mr. & Mrs. Wayne (Box 1)
  - Allred, Mrs. Floidene Hawkins (Box 1)
  - Allstate (Box 1)
  - Almanza, John (Box 1)
  - Alvey, Mrs. Opal M. (Box 1)
  - Alvin, Texas (Box 1)
  - Amacher, Judy (Mrs.) (Box 1)
  - American Association of Medical Assistants, inc. (Box 1)
  - American Association of State Colleges & Universities (Box 1)
  - American Association of University Women (Box 1)
  - American Bible Society (Box 1)
  - Americans for Constitutional Action (Box 1)
  - American Heart Association (Box 1)
  - American Industrial Bankers Asso. (Box 1)
  - American Institute of Architects (Box 1)
  - American National Bank (Box 1)
  - American Red Cross (Box 1)
  - American Revolution Bicennial Commission of Texas (Box 1)
  - Amon, Richard (Box 1)
  - Amos, Linda K. (Box 1)
  - Amtrak (Box 1)
  - Aaron, Miss Shirley (Box 2)
  - Abbott, Buek (Box 2)
  - Abdouch, Geo. (Box 2)
  - Abell, Bill W. (Box 2)
  - Abilene, Texas (Box 2)
  - Abraham, Malouf (Box 2)
  - Accident Investigation (Box 2)
  - Adair, Joe N. Jr. (Box 2)
  - Adams, Mr. B.T. (Box 2)
  - Adams, Rep. Don (Box 2)
  - Adeoek, Raymond (Box 2)
  - Ad Valorem Taxation Fees (Box 2)
  - Advertising (Box 2)
  - Advisory Commission on Inter Governmental Relations (Box 2)
  - African Violet Society (Box 2)
  - Aid to the Blind (Box 2)
  - Aid to Families with Dependent Children (Box 2)
  - Aid to the Permanently & totally Disabled (Box 2)
  - Ailes, O.T. (Box 2)
  - Ainsworth, Mr. Dan (Box 2)
  - Alamo (Box 2)
  - Alamo Iron Works (Box 2)
  - Albarado, Mr. Willis (Box 2)
  - Alcohol (Box 2)
  - Alcoholism (Box 2)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Commission (Box 2)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board (Box 2)
  - Alcoholism Council of Texas (Box 2)
  - Aldridge, Mrs. Mary (Box 2)
  - Alexander, Cecil (Box 2)
  - Alexander, paul (Box 2)
  - Alexander, Sue (Box 2)
  - Alford Refrigerated Warehouses, inc. (Box 2)
  - Ailes, Dollie E. (Box 2)
  - Allen, Mr. Gene (Box 2)
  - Allen, H. E. (Box 2)
  - Allen, Mr. & Mrs. J.R. (Box 2)
  - Allen, Mrs. L. V. (Box 2)
  - Allen, Michael E. (Box 2)
  - Allen, Vernon (Box 2)
  - Allen, Z. D. (Box 2)
  - Allison, Al (Box 2)
  - Allison, J.H. (Box 2)
  - Allison, Mr. Thurman (Box 2)
  - Allred, David Price (Box 2)
  - Allred, Johnny B. (Box 2)
  - Alsup, Jimmy (Box 2)
  - Altrusa, Club (Box 2)
  - Amalgamated Transit Union (Box 2)
  - Amarillo, Texas (Box 2)
  - Ambulance Services (Box 2)
  - American Association of Oilwell Drilling Contractors (Box 2)
  - American Association of Retired Persons (Box 2)
  - American Association of Workers for the Blind Inc. (Box 2)
  - American Automobile Assoc. (Box 2)
  - American Bar Association (Box 2)
  - American Cancer Society (Box 2)
  - American Civil Liberties Union (Box 2)
  - American College of Trial Lawyers (Box 2)
  - American Ex-Prisoners of War, Inc. (Box 2)
  - American Federation of Government Employees (Box 2)
  - American General Companies (Box 2)
  - American Income Life Insurance Company (Box 2)
  - American Marketing Association (Box 2)
  - American Raceways Inc. (Box 2)
  - American Society of Civil Engineers, Texas Section (Box 2)
  - American Trust Life Insurance Company (Box 2)
  - Americans for America (Box 2)
  - Americans for Democratic Action (Box 2)
  - Americanism Award (Box 2)
  - Amnon, Mr. Ricky (Box 2)
  - Amy, Mr. & Mrs. Douglas L. (Box 2)
  - Anderson, Mrs. A. E. (Box 2)
  - Anderson, Mr. Alfred T. (Box 2)
  - Anderson, Mr. & Mrs. Billy Don (Box 2)
  - Anderson, Dillard G. (Box 2)
  - Anderson, G. V. (Box 2)
  - Anderson, Mr. & Mrs. Henry (Box 2)
  - Anderson, Henry J., III (Box 2)
  - Anderson, Mrs. J. H. (Box 2)
  - Anderson, Marcus (Box 2)
  - Anderson, Mrs. Roy (Box 2)
  - Anderson, Mrs. Sue (Box 2)
  - Anderson, Mrs. Virginia (Box 2)
  - Anderson, W. T. (Box 2)
  - Andrews, Jim N. (Box 2)
  - Andrews, O. A. (Box 2)
  - Andrews, Welles U. (Box 2)
  - Andrus, Jim (Box 2)
  - Angelo State College (Box 2)
  - Angly, Maruice (Box 2)
  - Annual Session (Box 2)
  - Annuities (Box 2)
  - Ansohn, Mr. J. E. (Box 2)
  - Ansohn, W. L. (Box 2)
  - Anthony, Mrs. Merle (Box 2)
  - Anti-Crime Council of Texas (Box 2)
  - Antitrust Laws (Box 2)
  - Apple, Mr. & Mrs. Glenn (Box 2)
  - Appel, Mr. & Mrs. Herb (Box 2)
  - Applicants (Box 2)
  - Appropriations (Box 2)
  - Aransas Pass, Texas (Box 2)
  - Archer, Bill (Box 2)
  - Arlington State College (Box 2)
  - Armstrong Moving & Storage, Inc. (Box 2)
  - Armstrong, Bob (Box 2)
  - Armstrong, Mrs. Norma (Box 2)
  - Armstrong, Mr. & Mrs. Voyle (Box 2)
  - Arnold, C. Q. (Box 2)
  - Arnold, Mr. Marvis C. (Box 2)
  - Arnold, Mr. Royce (Box 2)
  - Arrow Coach Lines (Box 2)
  - Asphalt Roofing Industry (Box 2)
  - Ashley, Mrs. Tom (Box 2)
  - Assessments (Box 2)
  - Assistant District Atty. (Box 2)
  - Associated Federal Hotels (Box 2)
  - Associated General Contractors (Box 2)
  - Associated Tobacco Mfgrs. (Box 2)
  - Association of Consumer Finance Companies (Box 2)
  - Association of Texas Colleges & Universities (Box 2)
  - Association of Texas Fire & Casualty Companies (Box 2)
  - Aston, Dorothy (Box 2)
  - Atkins, Mr. & Mrs. Don (Box 2)
  - Atkins, Mr. James (Box 2)
  - Atkins, Dr. R. L. (Box 2)
  - Atkins, Mrs. Sam (Box 2)
  - Atterbury, Mrs. John H. (Box 2)
  - Attorney General (Box 2)
  - Attorneys (Box 2)
  - Atwood, Mr. & Mrs. A. C. (Box 2)
  - Audit Report Jan. 30, 1968 (Box 2)
  - Austin American (Box 2)
  - Austin Bureau (Box 2)
  - Austin Chamber of Commerce (Box 2)
  - Austin Clearing House Association (Box 2)
  - Austin, Mr. Mac (Box 2)
  - Austin Produce Company (Box 2)
  - Austin Report (Box 2)
  - Austin State Hospital (Box 2)
  - Auto Racing (Box 2)
  - Automatic Data Processing (Box 2)
  - Austin State School (Box 2)
  - Automobile Licenses (Box 2)
  - Automobile Manufactures Assn, Inc. (Box 2)
  - Automobile Safety (Box 2)
  - Auxiliary Police & Reserve Law Officers Assn. of Texas (Box 2)
  - Averyt, George (Box 2)
  - Avis, Mr. A. W. (Jake) (Box 2)
  - Ayers, Harry B. (Box 2)
  - Avery, Mrs. I. L. (Box 2)
  - Avrit, Paul W. Mrs. (Box 2)
  - Axline, G. H. (Bill) (Box 2)
  - Ayers, Miss Ella (Box 2)
  - Ayers, Golda (Box 2)
  - Association of Texas Soil & Water Conservation Districts (Box 3)
  - Astrodomain Corporation (Box 3)
  - Athletics (Box 3)
  - Atkins, Dan (Box 3)
  - Atkins, Mr. & Mrs. Hal (Box 3)
  - Atomic Energy Commission (Box 3)
  - Attorney General-North TX Regional Office (Box 3)
  - Atwell, Ben Mr. & Mrs. (Box 3)
  - Atwood, A. C. (Box 3)
  - Audiologists (Box 3)
  - Auld, Allie A. (Box 3)
  - Austin (Box 3)
  - Austin College (Box 3)
  - Austin, Stephen F. University (Box 3)
  - Avery, Glen (Box 3)
  - Aviation (Box 3)
  - Aviation Development Council of Texas (Box 3)
  - Avis, Burch (Mrs.) (Box 3)
  - Ayres, Mr. & Mrs. Jon (Box 3)
  - Anderson, Agnes (Box 3)
  - Anderson, Anna B. (Box 3)
  - Anderson, Dennis (Box 3)
  - Anderson, Faith C. (Ms.) (Box 3)
  - Anderson, George (Box 3)
  - Anderson, Mr. & Mrs. James C. (Box 3)
  - Anderson, Lola (Box 3)
  - Anderson, Sue L. (Box 3)
  - Andrews, Mr. & Mrs. Bobby (Box 3)
  - Andrews, C. (Box 3)
  - Andrews, Ernest L. (Box 3)
  - Andrews, Josie (Box 3)
  - Andrews, W. V. (Box 3)
  - Angleton, TX (Box 3)
  - Annapolis Research Corporation (Box 3)
  - Annual Legislative Sessions (Box 3)
  - Ansley, Mr. & Mrs. Lem (Box 3)
  - Anthony, Mrs. Marlin (Box 3)
  - Antwine, Mrs. Tommy (Box 3)
  - Appel, Herbert W., Jr. (Box 3)
  - Apperson, Fred L. (Box 3)
  - Application Forms (Box 3)
  - Aquarena Springs (Box 3)
  - Arceneaux, Ralph E. (Box 3)
  - Archer, Doris (Box 3)
  - Architects (Box 3)
  - Arias, Frank (Box 3)
  - Arnold, Albert (Box 3)
  - Arnold, Robert W. (Box 3)
  - Arp, Jack D. (Box 3)
  - Arrington, Modeline (Box 3)
  - Arthur, Dortha (Box 3)
  - Arthur, Mr. & Mrs. Lee (Box 3)
  - Asbury, John R. (M.D.) (Box 3)
  - Ashley, Calvin (Box 3)
  - Askings, Mrs. Sherry (Box 3)
  - Associated Milk Producers (Box 3)
  - Association for Children Learning Disabilities (ACLD) (Box 3)
  - Association for Retired People (Box 3)
  - Association of Texas Electric Cooperatives, inc. (Box 3)
  - Aaron, Mr. Cal (Box 3)
  - Aaron, Mr. Jack (Box 3)
  - AARP (Box 3)
  - AAS (Box 3)
  - Abadie, Margie M (Box 3)
  - Abbott, Mr. J. D. (Box 3)
  - Abbott, Mr. & Mrs. John T. (Box 3)
  - Abbott, Ms. Pauline O. (Box 3)
  - Abbott, S.L. (Rep.) (Box 3)
  - ABC Interstate Theatres, Inc. (Box 3)
  - Abernathy, Mrs. Betty (Box 3)
  - Able, Stephen Smith (Box 3)
  - Abortion 1970-1971 (Box 3)
  - Abortion 1971-1972 (Box 3)
  - Abortion 1973 (Box 3)
  - Abortion 1974-1975 (Box 3)
  - Abortion 1975 (Box 3)
  - Abortion 1978 (Box 3)
  - Abston, Al (Box 3)
  - A C Spark Plugs (Box 3)
  - Acker, Cliff (Box 3)
  - ACORN (Box 3)
  - ACME Employment Service (Box 3)
  - ACTION (Box 3)
  - Acton, Mrs. Dorthy (Box 3)
  - Acuff, Ms. Alma P. (Box 3)
  - Adair, Mr. & Mrs. Joe N. Sr. (Box 3)
  - Adams, Brian (Box 3)
  - Adair, Joe Jr. (Box 3)
  - Adams, Dovie (Box 3)
  - Adams, George J. (Box 3)
  - Adams, Mr. George R. (Box 3)
  - Adams, Mrs. Glen (Box 3)
  - Adams, James Glen (Box 3)
  - Adams, Linley W. (Box 3)
  - Adams, Louis C. (Box 3)
  - Adams, Norman B. (Box 3)
  - Adams, Ray (Box 3)
  - Addison, W. D. (Box 3)
  - Address Lists (Box 3)
  - Addy, Ms. Susan (Box 3)
  - Aderholt, Ms. Jeannie (Box 3)
  - Adjutant General (Box 3)
  - Administrative Procedure (Box 3)
  - Adult Probation Commission (Box 3)
  - Advocacy, Inc. (Box 3)
  - Agriculture File 1 (Box 4)
  - Agriculture File 2 (Box 4)
  - Agriculture Experiment Station (Box 4)
  - Agriculture Extension Service (Box 4)
  - Agricultural Stabilization & Conservation Service (Box 4)
  - Aikin, A. M. Jr. (Box 4)
  - Akin, William (Box 4)
  - Alaska State Legislature (Box 4)
  - Albany, TX (Box 4)
  - Albers, Mr. & Mrs. R. M. (Box 4)
  - Albin, Mrs. Doris (Box 4)
  - Alderman, Mrs. C. W. Jr. (Box 4)
  - Alderman, Gary (Box 4)
  - Aldridge, Arthur (Box 4)
  - Aldridge, Mrs. Gwendolyn (Box 4)
  - Aleshire, Bill (Box 4)
  - Alexander, Mrs. Florene (Box 4)
  - Alexander, Glenn D. (Box 4)
  - Alexander, Mr. Henry T. (Box 4)
  - Alexander, Ms. Julia (Box 4)
  - Allee, Henry E. (State Rep.) (Box 4)
  - Allen, Mrs. Cary (Box 4)
  - Allen, Mrs. Clyde K. (Box 4)
  - Allen, Mrs. David (Box 4)
  - Allen, Ernest (Box 4)
  - Allen, Mr. & Mrs. Frank (Box 4)
  - Allen, Mr. Jesse R. (Box 4)
  - Allen, Kay (Box 4)
  - Allen, L. W. (Box 4)
  - Allen, Mr Lonnie (Box 4)
  - Allen, Ms. Lynn (Box 4)
  - Allen, Ms. Maude J. (Box 4)
  - Allen, Mike (Box 4)
  - Allen, Wendell (Box 4)
  - Allen, Mr. Woofard H. (Box 4)
  - Allensworth, Martha (Box 4)
  - Allison, Mr. & Mrs. A. T. Jr. (Box 4)
  - Allison, Mr. Bob (Box 4)
  - Allison, Mrs. Koleta (Box 4)
  - Allison, Thelma Ann (Box 4)
  - Allmon, Ms. Elwanda (Box 4)
  - Alloggio, Lennie (Box 4)
  - Allred, Leland (Box 4)
  - Allred, Maurice L. (Box 4)
  - Alpha Personnel Agency of Wichita Falls (Box 4)
  - Alsobrook, Mr. & Mrs. Carl (Box 4)
  - Altendorf, Phil (Box 4)
  - Altman, Bill (Box 4)
  - Aluminum Co. of America (Box 4)
  - Ambrose, Ms. Audrey (Box 4)
  - Ambulances (Box 4)
  - American Assn. of Railroads (Box 4)
  - American Association of School Administrators (Box 4)
  - American Assn. of University Professors (Box 4)
  - American Biographical Institute (Box 4)
  - American Camping Assn. (Box 4)
  - American Federation of State, County, & Municipal Employees (Box 4)
  - American GI Forum (Box 4)
  - American Legion (Box 4)
  - American Legislative Exchange Council (Box 4)
  - American National Insurance Company (Box 4)
  - American Physical Therapy Assn. (Box 4)
  - American Registry of Certified Entomologists (Box 4)
  - American Society for Industrial Security (Box 4)
  - American Subcontractors Assn., Inc. (Box 4)
  - American Technological University (Box 4)
  - Ammons, James B. (Box 4)
  - Amnesty (Box 4)
  - Amnesty International (Box 4)
  - AMVETS (Box 4)
  - Anastopoulos, Mr. Billy (Box 4)
  - Anatomical Donors (Box 4)
  - Anderson, Mr. & Mrs. Carl T. (Box 4)
  - Anderson, D. M. (Box 4)
  - Anderson, David E. (Box 4)
  - Anderson, Ms. Frances (Box 4)
  - Anderson, Mrs. Gerald (Box 4)
  - Anderson, Mrs. Glenda (Box 4)
  - Anderson, Hank (Box 4)
  - Anderson, Mrs. J. R. (Box 4)
  - Anderson, Jean F. (Box 4)
  - Anderson, Jimmy (Box 4)
  - Anderson, John B. (Pres. Candidate) (Box 4)
  - Anderson, John Bureligh (Box 4)
  - Anderson, Owahah (Box 4)
  - Anderson, Stephen F. (Box 4)
  - Anderson, Verlan W. (Box 4)
  - Angell, Mrs. Ruth (Box 4)
  - Andre, Mr. Joseph J. (Box 4)
  - Andrews, Marjorie (Box 4)
  - Andrews, Noel Jr. (Box 4)
  - Anderson, Mr. Philip W. (Box 4)
  - Andrus, Buster (Box 4)
  - Andujar, Betty (Box 4)
  - Angelo State University (Box 4)
  - Angelo, Susan (Box 4)
  - Animals (Box 4)
  - Animal Health Commission (Box 4)
  - Annexation (Box 4)
  - Apple, Glen (Box 4)
  - Apple, Mrs. Jerry E. (Box 4)
  - Applegate, Ms. Gloria (Box 4)
  - Arlington, TX (Box 4)
  - Armed Forces (Box 4)
  - Armistead, Joseph D. (Maj.) (Box 4)
  - Armstrong, Mr. & Mrs. Gaylord (Box 4)
  - Armstrong, Ms. Marta (Box 4)
  - Armstrong, Mrs. R. H. Sr. (Box 4)
  - Army (Box 4)
  - Arndt, Mary & Ann (Box 4)
  - Arnhold, Dunc (Box 4)
  - Arrington, Joe (Box 4)
  - Arrington, Mrs. John (Box 4)
  - Arrowhead State Park (Box 4)
  - Arson (Box 4)
  - Art (Box 4)
  - Arwood, Mrs. Maurine (Box 4)
  - Ashley, Carlos (Box 4)
  - Ashley, Mr. & Mrs. W.C. Jr. (Box 4)
  - Ashlock, Mr. & Mrs. Jerry G. (Box 4)
  - Ashton, William (Box 4)
  - Asphalt Institute (Box 4)
  - Associated Builders & Contractors of Texas, Inc. (Box 4)
  - Associated Clubs & Lounges of Texas, Inc. (Box 4)
  - Associated Independent Electrical Contractors of Texas (Box 4)
  - Associated Security Services & Investigators of Texas (Box 4)
  - Association for Retarded Citizens, Texas (Box 4)
  - Association of oilwell servicing contractors (Box 4)
  - Association of Texas Educators (Box 4)
  - Allred, Mr. & Mrs. Renne Jr. File 1 (Box 5)
  - Allred, Mr. & Mrs. Renne Jr. File 2 (Box 5)
  - Allred, Mr. & Mrs. Renne Jr. File 3 (Box 5)
  - Allred, Mr. & Mrs. Renne Jr. File 4 (Box 5)
  - Allred, Mr. & Mrs. Renne Jr. File 5 (Box 5)
  - Allred, Mrs. Patricia Lee Moyer File 1 (Box 5)
  - Allred, Mrs. Patricia Lee Moyer File 2 (Box 5)
  - Allred, Mrs. Patricia Lee Moyer File 3 (Box 5)
  - Allred, Mrs. Patricia Lee Moyer File 4 (Box 5)
  - Allred, Mrs. Patricia Lee Moyer File 5 (Box 5)
  - Allred, Mrs. Patricia Lee Moyer File 6 (Box 5)
  - Allred, Mrs. Patricia Lee Moyer File 7 (Box 5)
  - Allred, John C. (Box 5)
  - Allred, Mrs. James V. (Box 5)
  - Allred, Ben (Box 5)
  - Allred, Renny (Box 5)
  - Allred, Joe Betsy (Box 5)
  - Allred, Renne Jr. (Box 5)
  - Allred, David (Box 5)
  - Allred, Raymon S. Jr. (Box 5)
  - Family (Box 5)
  - Research (Box 5)
  - Allred, Dave (Box 5)
  - Alexander, Dr. & Mrs. James (Box 5)
  - Attorney General's Office (Box 5)
  - Astrodome (Box 6)
  - Athiests (Box 6)
  - Atkins, Patricia L. (Box 6)
  - Atkinson, Hamp (Box 6)
  - Atlantic Richfield (Box 6)
  - Attorney Generals Office (Box 6)
  - Attruis, Pat (Box 6)
  - Attwood, Mrs. Robert (Box 6)
  - Auctions (Box 6)
  - Auctioneers (Box 6)
  - Aulds, A.C. (Box 6)
  - Ausanka, Frank (Box 6)
  - Ausley, Mrs. Happy (Box 6)
  - Austin (Box 6)
  - Austin, Mrs. Loraine (Box 6)
  - Austin National Bank (Box 6)
  - Austin, Ms. Rosie (Box 6)
  - Auto Safety (Box 6)
  - Automobiles (Box 6)
  - Avara, Mrs. Bonnie (Box 6)
  - Avenius, Mrs. Tanna (Box 6)
  - Avenius, Victor (Box 6)
  - Averitt, Mrs. Edgar (Box 6)
  - Ayer, Mrs. Steve (Box 6)
  - Ayers, Mr. Eugene M. (Box 6)
  - Ayres, Jerry (Box 6)
  - Ayers, O. W. (Box 6)
  - Ayres, Pam (Box 6)
  - Adding Machine Papers (Box 6)
  - Almeida, Norma (Box 6)
  - American National Bank of Austin (Box 6)
  - American Security & Trust Co. (Box 6)
  - Anderson, Robert (Box 6)
  - Arlington House (Box 6)
  - Armbruster, Annie S. (Box 6)
  - Arpe, Mr. & Mrs. Bill (Box 6)
  - Assistant Deacons (Box 6)
  - Associated Press (Box 6)
  - Babb, Charlie M. (Box 6)
  - Baber, Jerry (Box 6)
  - Babinsky, Ms. Marlene (Box 6)
  - Bachman Mrs. Stewart Jr. (Box 6)
  - Backdoor Theatre (W.F.) (Box 6)
  - Bacon, Mr. & Mrs. G.W. (Box 6)
  - Bacus, Mr. Tom (Box 6)
  - Badiei, Dr. Badiolah (Box 6)
  - Baggett, Edwin (Box 6)
  - Bahme, Mrs. Louise Barney (Box 6)
  - Bail Bonds (Box 6)
  - Bailey, Mrs. C. L. (Box 6)
  - Bailey, H. Deloyd (Box 6)
  - Bailey, Herman (Box 6)
  - Bailey, Mrs. Jeannette (Box 6)
  - Bailey, Kay (Box 6)
  - Bailey, Ms. Renei (Box 6)
  - Bailey, Weldon (Box 6)
  - Baird, Margeret (Box 6)
  - Bait (Box 6)
  - Baker, A.C. (Box 6)
  - Baker, Ms. Betty J. (Box 6)
  - Baker, Mrs. Emma B. (Box 6)
  - Baker, George (Box 6)
  - Bailey, Martha (Box 6)
  - Baker, R. M. (Box 6)
  - Baker Duncan Van & Storage Company (Box 6)
  - Balch, Mrs. Myrtle (Box 6)
  - Baldwin, Ms. Bertha (Box 6)
  - Baber, Mr. & Mrs. Hertis (Box 6)